A Guide to the Louis Arthur Johnson Papers, ca. 1930-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series V. Papers of the Secretary of Defense
  - Subseries A, General Correspondence
    - Correspondence with Doctor Donald Balfour 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Doctor Allen Barker 1949 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Alben W. Barkley, the Vice-President of the United States 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Bernard M. Baruch 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Karl R. Bendetsen 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with M. L. Benedum 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with William Benton, Senator 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Adolf A. Berle, Jr. 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with J. Raymond Berry, General Counsel, the National Board of Fire Underwriters 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with James T. Berryman 1949 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Remster Bingham 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with G. D. Birla, industrialist of India 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Van. A. Bittner, vice-president of CIO United Steelworkers 1949 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with James B. Black 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Jacob Blaustein 1949 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with various dignitaries re: Bohemian Grove Encampment, July 1949 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Admiral J. T. Boone 1949 (Box 102)
    - TL (carbon), Monroe Schaff to Frank W. Boykin 1950 Aug. 11 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with James A. Branch 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Charles F. Brannan 1949 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with W. M. Breed 1950 Sept. (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Owen Brewster, U. S. Senate 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Louis Bromfield 1949 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Overton Brooks 1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with William E. Brooks, author, lecturer, and leader in the Presbyterian Church 1949-1950 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence with Gerald B. Brophy 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Clarence J. Brown, Congressman 1950 (Box 103)
    - CWO Drew E. Brown, Classified Files OSD; Personal and Confidential Files of Sec. Of Defense Johnson re: a variety of official topics 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Maxwell Brown, Congressman 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Paul Brown, Congressman 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Thomas G. Brown 1950 Sept. (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with James Bruce, former U. S. Ambassador to the Argentine Republic; Director of the Mutual Defense Assistance Program 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with John M. Budinger 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Usher L. Burdick, Congressman 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Carter L. Burgess, General Aniline and Film Corp. 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with E. H. Burgess, vice-president, The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with General J. H. Burns 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Robert Butler, The American Embassy, Cuba 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Senator Harry F. Byrd 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with George T. Cameron, The San Francisco Chronicle 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Alex Campbell, Assistant Attorney General 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with C. Cannon, American Ambassador, State Dept. 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Champ Carry 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Amon Carter, Fort Worth Star-Telegram 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with John Cartwright 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Elizabeth Cather 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Wm. M. Chadbourne 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Stephen F. Chadwick 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Lafe B. Chafin, Prosecuting Attorney's Office 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Howard Chandler Christy 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Oscar Chapman 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with [?] Chiang 1950 May (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with James R. Childs, American Ambassador 1949 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with various people re: Christmas greetings, 2 folders 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence re: Citizens Committee for the Army and Navy, Inc. Award presentation 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Tom Clark, Justice Supreme Court of the United States and former Attorney General 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Brooke Claxton, Minister of National Defense, Canada 1949-1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Clark M. Clifford 1950 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence with Jacqueline Cochran (Mrs. Floyd B. Odlum) 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with O. S. Colclough 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Charles Collingwood, CBS 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with General J. Lawton Collins 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with U. S. Senate Committee on Banking and Currency re: S. 3936, Defense Production Act 1950 Aug. 11-14 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Karl Compton 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Colonel Rollo C. Conley 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Charles P. Cooper 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with John J. Cornwell 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Myron Cowan, American Embassy, Manila, Philippine Islands 1949-1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Ronald M. Craigmyle 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Joan S. Crane 1950 Sept. (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Sir Stafford Cripps, Treasury, London, England 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Luige Criscuolo, Chairman, American Italian Congress 1950 Sept. (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Willis D. Crittenberger 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Robert Crosser, Congressman 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with General Benedict Crowell 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with R. Granville Curry 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Mr. Snydam Cutting 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Franklin D'Olier 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with R. S. Damon 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Colgate W. Darden, Jr. 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Joseph E. Davies 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Elmer Davis, American Broadcasting Company 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with George A. Davis 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Mr. R. S. Davis, Universal Glass Products Co. 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Charles G. Dawes 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Gordon Dean, Atomic Energy Commission 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Albert Deveze, Minister of National Defense, Belgium 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Thomas E. Dewey, Governor, State of N. Y. 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Walter F. Dillingham 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Armistead M. Dobie 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Lewis W. Douglas 1949-1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Paul H. Douglas, Senator 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Michael F. Doyle, Attorney 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Lloyd Dumas 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Edgar B. Dunlap 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Samuel C. Dunlap 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Stephen T. Early, Deputy Secretary of Defense 1949-1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Robert Easton 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with F. Eberstadt 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Marriner S. Eccles, Federal Reserve System 1949 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with David Edelstein, Assistant Attorney General of the United States 1950 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence with Dwight D. Eisenhower 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Mark Eisner 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Herbert B. Elliston, The Washington Post1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence re: Equality of Treatment and Opportunity in the Armed Services 1940-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with James A. Farley 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with General Philip B. Fleming, U. S. Maritime Commission 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Robert D. Flory 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with James F. Fogarty 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Peyton Ford, Assistant to the Attorney General 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. James V. Forrestal 1950 March 21 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Fort Omaha property, Omaha, Nebraska 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with James D. Francis 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Warren B. Francis, Los Angeles Times1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with John M. Franklin, United States Lines 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with William Frye Director of Public Information, Department of Defense 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Walter D. Fuller, Curtis Publishing Co. 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Leon W. George 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Amadeo Peter Giannini, Transamerica Corp., Bank of Virginia 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with L. M. Giannini, Bank of America 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Guy M. Gillette, Senator 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Earl B. Gilmore 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Brig. Gen. Robert Ginsburgh 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Tom M. Girdler 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with John B. Glenn 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Earl Godwin 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Samuel Goldwyn 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Edward B. Gordon 1950 Sept. 11 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with George J. Gould 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Marshall C. Graff 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Philip Graham 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Gorden Gray, the Secretary of the Army 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Colonel Paul Griffith 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence re: Bohemian Grove, Midsummer Encampment 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with James M. Guiher, Steptoe & Johnson 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Chan Gurney, U. S. Senate 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with W. Averell Harriman 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Harriet Meade Hass 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Lowell H. Hattery, The American University 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Jens Christian Hauge, Minister of Defense of Norway 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Erland Hedrick, Congressman 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Sissy Barth Heistand 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Louis B. Heller, Congressman 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Robert Heller 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Arthur Herrington 1950 April July (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Paul M. Herzag, National Labor Relations Board 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Charles Colby Hewitt 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Downey Hines 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Harold Hinton 1949 May (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Sam Hobbs, Congressman 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Richard W. Hoffman, Congressman 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Wm. B. Hogg, attorney 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with John W. Hollister 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Homer A. Holt, Union Carbide and Carbon Corp. 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Herbert Hoover 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with J. Edgar Hoover 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Russell J. Hopley, Northwestern Bell Telephone 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Harold J. T. Horan 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Emma Hornor 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Roy W. Howard, Scripps-Howard Newspapers 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Charles R. Howell, Congressman 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Palmer Hoyt, The Denver Post1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Arthur M. Hughes, West Side Presbyterian Church 1950 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Cordell Hull 1949 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with George Hutton 1950 Sept. (Box 105)
    - Correspondence with Harold L. Ickes 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Donald Jackson, Congressman 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Colonel H. Nelson Jackson 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Robert H. Jamison 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Mertie McDonald John 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Edwin C. Johnson, U. S. Senate 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with F. L. Johnson 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Robert B. Johnson 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with General Robert W. Johnson, Johnson & Johnson 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Olin D. Johnston, Senator 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Harold A. Jones 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Doctor H. H. K'ung 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with H. V. Kaltenborn 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Irving Kaufman, U. S. District Court, New York 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with James S. Kemper 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with John A. Kennedy, San Diego Journal1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with William P. Kennedy, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Frank Kent, The Baltimore Sun1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with A. N. Kemp, Pacific Mutual Life Insurance Company 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Harly M. Kilgore, U. S. Senate 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with [] [King] 1949 April (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Robert E. Kintner, American Broadcasting Company 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Alfred P. Knapp 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with John T. Koehler, Assistant Secretary of the Navy 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Weaden C. Koon, Veterinarian 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with K. R. Kreps, Colonel, USAF 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Arthur F. Kroeger 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Harry Jutik 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Chaman Lal, author 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Gordon Lamont 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Harry Lang 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Doctor Frank v. Langfitt 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with C. T. Lanham, Brigadier General, U. S. A. 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Mr. Jack Lann 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with R. D. Lapham 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Jess Larson, Federal Works Administrator 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Robert Lawson 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with H. M. Lay 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with George LaVallee 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Paul R. Leach, Knight Newspapers 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Edward L. Leahy, Senator 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Charles H. Leavy, U. S. District Judge 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Herbert L. Lehman 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Admiral Lewis 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with John L. Lewis 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Edmond E. Lincoln 1949-1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr. 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with William T. Lovins, Judge 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with General Frank E. Lowe 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Jim Lucas, Scripps-Howard Newspaper Alliance 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Scott W. Lucas 1950 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Lauren D. Lyman, United Aircraft Corp. 1949 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence with Lillie McAndrews, National Board of Fire Underwriters 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with General MacArthur 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Carl W. McCardle, The Evening Bulletin1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with John J. McCloy 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with John McCone 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Robert R. McCormick, Chicago Tribune1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Harry McDonald 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Admiral Ross T. McIntire, U. S. Department of Labor 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Gilbert MacKay 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with W. J. McNeil 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Wm. K. Macy 1950 (Box 107)
    - Memorandum with enclosure re: Mr. Mahon's speech on the U. S. military situation and Korea 1950 Aug. 25, Sept. 7 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with W. C. Marland 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with General George C. Marshall 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Francis P. Matthews, Secretary of the Navy 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Maury Maverick re: the great seal of the U. S. 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Burnet R. Maybank, Senator 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with George Meany 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Merrill C. Meigs, the Hearst Corporation 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Richard L. Meiling 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Perle Mesta, United States Minister to Luxembourg 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Memoranda re: MATS (Military Air Transport Service) 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with T. E. Millsop, Weirton Steel Company 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Justice Sherman Minton 1949 (Box 107)
    - Message from Ronald Moist 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Robert H. Mollohan 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with C. A. Montgomery, Aviation Committee 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Henry Morgenthau, Jr. 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Stanley C. Morris, attorney with Steptoe and Johnson 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Wayne Morse, Senator 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Walter J. Munro 1949 (Box 107)
    - Mrs. Mary Murray to Mrs. Louis Johnson 1950 Aug. 15 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Unni Nayar 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Matthew M. Neely, Senator 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with R. K. Nehru, Legation of India 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with various people re: New Year Greetings 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Clyde M. Newhouse 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Admiral Chester Nimitz 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with W. F. Norrell 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Mary T. Norton, Congressman 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Basil O'Connor 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with William O'Dwyer, Mayor, New York City 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence re: Offers of Services (Individuals or Companies), Korean Crisis 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with John Ohly 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Thomas W. O'Hara 1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Michael J. O'Neill, General Counsel, Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. 1949-1950 (Box 107)
    - Memo from A. H. Onthank 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Victor Orestes 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with James B. L. Orme 1950 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with John Osborne, Life Magazine1949 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence with Frank Pace, Jr., Secretary of the Army 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Frank C. Page, International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Madame Vijaya Lakshmi Pandit, Ambassador of India 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Maj. J. R. Parten, Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Ira J. Partlow, Judge 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Richard C. Patterson, American Embassy, Guatemala 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Robert P. Patterson 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Edwin W. Pauley 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Calling Cards of Dasturzada Paury and Miss Bapsy Paury 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with William D. Pawley 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Stuyvesant Peabody 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Cloyce Pearson 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with John Peurifoy 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Miss Philibert 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Harold K. Philips 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Rev. W. E. Pierce 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Poor's Register of Directors and Executives 1949 (Box 108)
    - Request from the Press for a background session in Paris [1950] March 30 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Samuel Pryor, Jr. 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Elpidio Quirino 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Robert Ramspeck 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with A. Philip Randolph, Committee against Jim Crow in Military Service [1950?] (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with B. Shiva Rao, India Delegation to the United Nations 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with General Milton A. Reckford 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Daniel A. Reed 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Justice Stanley Reed 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with William S. Renchard 1950 (Box 108)
    - Memorandum re: Reproduction of the Secretary's Flag 1950 June 16 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with H. G. Rhawn, the Clarksburg News1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with F. D. G. Ribble 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with F. H. Richardson 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with E. V. Rickenbacker, Eastern Air Lines 1949 (Box 108)
    - Biographical note on General Sir Neil Ritchie [ca. 1949?] (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with L. Mendel Rivers, Congressman 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Owen J. Roberts 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with A. Willis Robertson, Senator 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Hugo E. Rogers, attorney 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with William P. Rogers, Senator 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr. 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Sol. A. Rosenblatt 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with M. M. Rosten 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Kenneth C. Royall, Attorney, former Secretary of the Army 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with E. H. Rynearson 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Noel Sargent, National Post-War Conference 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Charles Sawyer, Secretary of Commerce 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with W. A. Schmitt 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Frank D. Schroth, publisher, the Brooklyn Eagle1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Tom Schully 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with the Right Reverend Maurice S. Sheehy 1949 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with John F. Shelley, Congressman 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Admiral Forest Sherman 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Robert Sherrod, Time, Inc. 1949-1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Emanuel Shinwell, Minister of Defense, England 1950 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence with Max Siskind 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Charles P. Skouras 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with John Slack 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. William Slocum, National Broadcasting Co. 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with George Smathers 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Frederick C. Smith, Congressman 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with H. Alexander Smith Senator 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Harold V. Smith 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with General W. B. Smith 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with John Snyder, Secretary of the Treasury 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Benjamin Sonnenberg 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence re: the decision by the Administration to intervene actively in South Korea, 2 folders 1950 June-Aug. (Box 109)